{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040250324","data":{"timestamp":" 947040250323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040252458","data":{"timestamp":" 947040252457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040254589","data":{"timestamp":" 947040254588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040257813","data":{"timestamp":" 947040257812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040260086","data":{"timestamp":" 947040260086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040262364","data":{"timestamp":" 947040262363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040265255","data":{"timestamp":" 947040265255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040267481","data":{"timestamp":" 947040267481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040269713","data":{"timestamp":" 947040269713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040273060","data":{"timestamp":" 947040273060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040275182","data":{"timestamp":" 947040275182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040277292","data":{"timestamp":" 947040277292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040280277","data":{"timestamp":" 947040280276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040282525","data":{"timestamp":" 947040282525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040284681","data":{"timestamp":" 947040284681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040287711","data":{"timestamp":" 947040287711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040290071","data":{"timestamp":" 947040290070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040292408","data":{"timestamp":" 947040292407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040295505","data":{"timestamp":" 947040295504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040297641","data":{"timestamp":" 947040297640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040299811","data":{"timestamp":" 947040299810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040302978","data":{"timestamp":" 947040302977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040305190","data":{"timestamp":" 947040305189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040307409","data":{"timestamp":" 947040307409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040310585","data":{"timestamp":" 947040310585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040313011","data":{"timestamp":" 947040313010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040315454","data":{"timestamp":" 947040315454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040318752","data":{"timestamp":" 947040318751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040321047","data":{"timestamp":" 947040321046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040323287","data":{"timestamp":" 947040323287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040326390","data":{"timestamp":" 947040326389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040328648","data":{"timestamp":" 947040328647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040330997","data":{"timestamp":" 947040330996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040333993","data":{"timestamp":" 947040333993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040336459","data":{"timestamp":" 947040336458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040338839","data":{"timestamp":" 947040338838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040341987","data":{"timestamp":" 947040341986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040344376","data":{"timestamp":" 947040344376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040346750","data":{"timestamp":" 947040346749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040349733","data":{"timestamp":" 947040349733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040352151","data":{"timestamp":" 947040352150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040354459","data":{"timestamp":" 947040354458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040357737","data":{"timestamp":" 947040357736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040360137","data":{"timestamp":" 947040360137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040362423","data":{"timestamp":" 947040362422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040365784","data":{"timestamp":" 947040365784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040368250","data":{"timestamp":" 947040368249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040370845","data":{"timestamp":" 947040370845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040373741","data":{"timestamp":" 947040373740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040376088","data":{"timestamp":" 947040376087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040378264","data":{"timestamp":" 947040378263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040381714","data":{"timestamp":" 947040381714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040384045","data":{"timestamp":" 947040384044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040386393","data":{"timestamp":" 947040386392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040389549","data":{"timestamp":" 947040389549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040391788","data":{"timestamp":" 947040391787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040394029","data":{"timestamp":" 947040394029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040396965","data":{"timestamp":" 947040396965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040399040","data":{"timestamp":" 947040399040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040401130","data":{"timestamp":" 947040401130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_054351"," gameId":" 9fc237ab-9b55-49f2-a1ee-99360cd24659"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}